<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[ATMAYOGA]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[ATMAYOGA]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/unyoga/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 02:12:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/unyoga/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Posture Clinic]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Posture Clinic</h1><h2>Part 1 What is the human body? Connective tissue Muscles Joints Nervous system Part 2How do you maintain it? Move it (joints, glands, connective tissue) Use it (muscle contraction and lengthening-aerobic and anaerobic) Relax it (nervous sustem and muscles) Feed it (total system) 15 principal poses and their musculoskeletal purpose Sanskrit vocabulary of each pose with pronunciation Physical description/breakdown of each pose Benefits and risks of each Teaching action cues of each Adjustments criteria safety when to and when not to Sequencing rules anatomical issues execution Scripting developing scripts (languaging your sequence) preparing for teaching</h2><p>4 day bootcamp – $500Anatomy – The language of the body</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/083e25ca-4cac-4b66-84f0-a0f8661a4120.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://vimeo.com/98123388</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ededa9b4-3004-41da-bf00-2c28f35265d1</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 02:12:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[History  5000 years ago  150 years ago  40 years ago  Today    Philosophy  Six Sanskrit philosophies one goal  Vedanta – a progressive and adaptive ideology  Yoga – Patanjali the ancient path, Bhakti the modern path  Samkya – a model for virtual reality ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/943819b6-7d57-42cf-9f88-247b4296b45f.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://travelaway.me/cool-travel-gadgets/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">01c09797-7b12-4a90-b99e-28e020fb46da</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 01:44:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[5 must-visit destinations in Patagonia for modern explorers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>5 must-visit destinations in Patagonia for modern explorers</h1><p>Patagonia's 400,000 square miles are home to some of the most beautiful and diverse landscapes on the planet. It's an ideal destination for adventure seekers and one of our top destinations for travel in 2016. This expansive area of land, spread across southern Chile and Argentina, is too much to take in all at once.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e6efb0a3ccb646f900a2bfa7ce773939dbc12ab9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mashable.com/2016/04/05/patagonia-adventure-travel/#GmuWjVf0GZqo</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9f10ac37-1e94-42d5-a24c-cc9e73b3621e</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 01:20:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>